quiz_data_3 = [
    {
        "question": "Which of these strategies are valid in managing a traffic accident?",
        "choices": ["Exiting the Vehicle as Soon as Possible", "Making Sure the Car's Ignition is on", "Sending a Person Up the Road to Warn Traffic", "Lighting Area with High Beam Lights"],
        "answer": "Sending a Person Up the Road to Warn Traffic"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which of these are not part of managing an incident in a water environment?",
        "choices": ["Sending for Help Immediately", "Using Surrounding Branches or Environemnt", "Assessing Self Limitations", "Only Engaging in Rescue with More Than One Person"],
        "answer": "Only Engaging in Rescue with More Than One Person"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first priority in giving treatment in an environemnt with a live wire?",
        "choices": ["Treat Affected Patient", "Turn Off Power Source", "Clean Any Spilled Liquids", "Turn Off Any Lights in the Room"],
        "answer": "Turn Off Power Source"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fluid can HIV/AIDS not be passed through?",
        "choices": ["Blood", "Urine", "Semen", "Mucus"],
        "answer": "Urine"
    },
    {
        "question": "How can you prevent HIV transmission when performing CPR",
        "choices": ["Avoid Contact with Casualty as much as Possible", "Cover Casualty's Mouth with a Face Mask Prior to CPR", "Use Oils and Lotions on Hands as a Barrier to Infection", "Perform Hands-only CPR"],
        "answer": "Cover Casualty's Mouth with a Face Mask Prior to CPR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is illegal in relation to First Aid?",
        "choices": ["Not Acting to Administer CPR", "Unconsensual Treatment", "Using Excessive Force", "Advertising and Performing under Fake Certifications"],
        "answer": "Advertising and Performing under Fake Certifications"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does debriefing involve?",
        "choices": ["Obtaining Information About the Incident Requiring First Aid", "Informing a Patient of any Treatment they have Received", "Notifying Bystanders of the Casualty's Situation", "Contacting Medical Services for the Patient"],
        "answer": "Obtaining Information About the Incident Requiring First Aid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the effects of administering First Aid on a person's mental health?",
        "choices": ["Anxiety", "Low Brain Stimulation", "Inability to Regulate Hormones", "Paralysis"],
        "answer": "Anxiety"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a method that can help first aiders deal with mental health?",
        "choices": ["Practicing Treatment Techniques", "Mentoring other First Aiders", "Medications", "Counselling"],
        "answer": "Counselling"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "choices": [" Hepatitis A, Hepatitis C and Hepatitis D", "Hepatitis B, Hepatitis C and Hepatitis D", "Hepatitis A, Hepatitis B and Hepatitis E", "Hepatitis A, Hepatitis B and Hepatitis C" ],
        "answer": "Hepatitis A, Hepatitis B and Hepatitis C"
    }
    # Add more questions here
]